travelbuoy.com 2012-10-21

# Privacy Policy | Travelbuoy

TravelBuoy.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. The following policy will help you understand how your personal information will be treated as you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. This policy is subject to change from time to time so please check back periodically.

#### Overview

TravelBuoy.com . is a leading provider featured departments on Attire, Laptops,Software,Travel,Jewels,Auto, Gadgets,small business and Finance. This Overall Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire TravelBuoy.com website.

#### Statement

TravelBuoy.com respects your right to privacy. Because we gather certain types of information about our users we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather and how we use it.

#### What Information does TravelBuoy.com collect ?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Because we derive revenue mainly from advertising, collecting information is essential to keep our services affordable to users.

We collect personal information about our users during usage of the TravelBuoy.com service, from our use of ‘cookie’ technology as you use the service and during viewing through TravelBuoy.com or while subscribing to our newsletter and special offer services.

#### What is TravelBuoy.com ‘s practice regarding cookies ?

Your Internet browser has a feature called “cookies” which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to Internet websites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit TravelBuoy.com . Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information which we may use to enhance your services in the ways described below. You may choose not to allow cookies to be collected by adjusting your settings on your browser.

We use technologies, including electronic images known as Web beacons (called a transparent GIF or single-pixel GIF) that allow us to track general user traffic patterns. We also automatically receive and record information from our servers and from your browser, including your IP address, the time of your visit to pages on our website, and information about pages you visited. The information we gather through the use of tracking technologies cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you unless you have specifically given us personally identifiable information. We may use the information to enhance your services in the ways described below.

  * __We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including:
  * __Keeping count of return visits to our website or our advertisers’ or partners’ websites.
  * __Accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on website and advertisement usage.
  * __Determining which features our overall user population likes best.
  * __Saving your name & e-mail address so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our website.
  * __Display the most appropriate advertising based on your interests.

We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on our websites and, sometimes, in our newsletters to use tracking technology on your computer. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Unless you visit the website of these companies and provide them with personally identifiable information about yourself, these tracking technologies tell those advertisers nothing about who you are. Our advertisers’ use of tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies.

#### How does TravelBuoy.com use the information it collects ?

We use the information we gather for the following purposes:

  * __To customize the advertising and content you see
  * __To enhance the user experience in our website. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.
  * __To fulfill your requests for fresh content and services.
  * __To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.

#### How does TravelBuoy.com share this information and with whom ?

We aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional, and other purposes. We do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. For example, we may tell our business partners how many customers in certain demographic groups used our services.

#### What is TravelBuoy.com ‘s practice regarding IP addresses ?

We collect and analyze traffic on our website by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.

TravelBuoy.com uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to third parties we believe to be responsible. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. TravelBuoy.com also links to a wide variety of other websites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

#### How does TravelBuoy.com handle 3rd Party Advertising ?

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Our third-party advertising companies also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit their respective privacy policies.

#### Questions and Comments

If you have any questions, comments or suggestions regarding our website’s privacy policy, or regarding any other aspects of our website, please write to us.

#### Notification of Changes

Please note that any changes in the Privacy Policy will be posted here.
